- Wow, you had a hard time
- Thank you for your hard work.
It's all thanks to you, senior.
- Uh
- Oh, yes.
Uh, mom
Hey!
Why didn't you say you were broadcasting?
You almost missed it
Have you seen Mom? Am I broadcasting?
I saw it, then
My daughter’s face after a long time
It was so good to see it on TV
I've been hiding that talent for a long time.
how hard was it
Mom, I'm going to be on broadcast from now on.
It will come out consistently, so be sure to watch it
Ah!
and
I did so well today
The managing director said to broadcast it right away?
okay?
After all, my daughter
Who do you resemble like this?
I don't know if it'll break
Huh?
No PD
The one in Najeong’s unnie’s suite.
You don’t like it, right?
Can't you let me go?
what?
I knew it would be like this
Ah, so I can somehow
Najeong comes in
Please don't let me do it
I apologize to PD.
Ah, but why
Did you chew my words? why?
Hey, you got hurt.
Is it because of Na-jeong?
Oh, of course!
My sister took an outdoor photo shoot
Even if I didn’t just say let’s do it
I wonder if I ended up like this!
Oh, what, so?
Me and Najeong, really.
We can't work together
Even now, the producer spoke well.
Najeong, tell me to stop
Can't I do it?
what?
Oh, honestly, that's right.
Producer Noh is also because of Seonmin.
This was filmed at No PD’s company.
Najeong unni
You don't want to find out
- I'm dying of discomfort too...
- Hey, Song Yena
you me
Because I stay still
Does this person look funny?
The chosen people's work is the chosen people's work.
What do you think about Na-jeong?
Talking carelessly
Doesn't that leave a line?
Wow, people are so stubborn
Intimately for the first time in a while
Let's go in after dinner.
Yeeun is
Didn't you hear from me when I was coming in?
Ah, with my daughter.
It's been a long time since I had dinner
Hey, you guys
It’s been a while for you guys, guys.
I did that
I told you not to touch it!
I'm surprised...
No, this is about equity.
Isn't that too out of line?
Ah, why are we the same intern?
Someone let me broadcast it
Who is allowed to just observe?
That's right
Oh, and it's not even a sub.
Alone?
That's because the main one was stung by a bee
- I heard you blocked it with a pinch hitter?
- under!
Stung by a bee? tooth
Even if the lucky bitch takes a step back
They say you catch a frog
Oh!
good morning!
Good morning to everyone
Let's go get some coffee or something.
Good
Ugh!
Why isn't there one?
Ah... that
From the next program, you
When I asked her to be a sub, Yena
When you think about it, you still
They said it was impossible and asked us to put it on hold.
As you know, the issue of equity is also
It's a problem
Even the mentor opposed it.
Because there is no reason
yes
Ah, there...
Have you not seen Song Yena?
It looks like he's resting in the waiting room.
uh, thank you
What are you doing now?
What are you doing?
They all look like they're going to die
take me to the emergency room
I stopped the broadcast from going flat.
Do you return favor with vengeance?
Are you still human?
Can it be interpreted that way again?
What about your sister?
Because my sister and I fall into the gutter
It looks like you stepped on it?
under! True
Ouch! Okay, let's not talk.
Just like you, I twisted everything up like that.
How can a thinking person be harmed?
It's done
From now on you
Whether you fall into the gutter or end up dead,
I will never help you
The day I help you again
It's not a human baby
Oh...
Wow! Man, I’m pissed.
What enemies did you have in your past life?
Are you going to risk everything like this?
Anyway
I didn't save him!
You knew it
That bitch is such a bitch
I knew it but
I didn't know it was this bad, ah!
What can you do?
I somehow consoled him and comforted him
I shouldn’t make a big deal out of it.
no, no
I'm like those guys
I know because I’ve experienced it a lot.
If those insignificant kids go out hard,
Do you often get angry?
How about attacking head on instead?
What kind of head-on?
Just because of workplace harassment
Report it!
- what?
- A
Isn't that too risky a solution?
What's dangerous?
If it stays like this anyway,
It's obvious that I won't get any points and will be fired.
If that's the case, it's better to attack head on!
Don't talk nonsense
Anyway
Yena Song is an employee and this one is an intern.
Accusation? Easier said than done
Who in the company will support you?
Who do you think will suffer that disadvantage?
So, what should I do?
I would rather roast him and boil him.
think of a way
Hey
Strictly speaking,
Aren't you a saleswoman?
Attracting even uninterested viewers
Can't you just seduce him?
That's right
Huh? That's right
Have you been to an obstetrician/gynecologist?
Uh, uh
They say it's menstrual irregularity
Oh no
I knew you would
Hey, I stay up all night every day
I drank too much and worked hard.
Hey, we're just living now
You shouldn't do that.
If you live a lifeless life when you are young
As I get older
My body is taking revenge on me!
Oh, okay! okay!
Ah, what should I do?
Aww, I'm pissed
Where are you, driver?
Arriving in about 5 minutes?
Are you not going to tell Na-jeong?
Well, it’s nothing, I’m worried for no reason.
It's obvious to make a fuss
Maybe...
Why not try egg freezing?
What are you doing?
I have no intention of having children.
Still
Maybe later
When you meet someone you really love
You might change your mind
Egg freezing?
Uh...
Well, it's completely impossible
No, it's not.
Just work hard
You may not have much success.
Usually about 20 follicles
Need to collect
One or two of them
Because it's about success.
But Illy Lee
Because follicle creation itself is difficult
That's it! Why is it over?
Honey, are you here?
uh
Uh, then take a shower and rest.
Did you drink honey?
uh
Do you like it?
uh?
I don't want to have children
Is it okay to drink and go around?
What's wrong again?
honey
What's wrong?
Why do you find this funny?
I'm not even a kid
Why is this fun?
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
What happened?
yes
Let's quit
It's just a doll...
Just because of workplace harassment
Report it!
Rather
You can roast and boil him
think of a way
Strictly speaking,
Aren't you a saleswoman?
Oh, what should I do?
uh!
Uh, hello!
I'm your fan.
Oh!
what? Hey, Jo Na-jeong
I said it would rain
When should I flatter you?
What's the deal with a bitch like that?
You also got screwed as a guest.
They say it needs to be filled
Home shopping is also the forefront of shopping.
There is also a common denominator
Show host too
It's a semi-celebrity-like job.
I got caught up in a bitch like a fox
Maybe I'm just having a hard time
Let's just think simply!
This isn't him
for our careers
Highly strategic tactics
Same thing, huh?
Oh, I wanted to talk about something else.
Call someone out?
Oh, speak quickly, I'm busy.
Yeah, yeah
Because I don’t want to see you too long
I'll just state the matter briefly.
Come on, we
Stop this childish war of attrition
How about going a little more strategically?
Excluding selfishness
In a win-win direction
What are you talking about?
Speak so that you can understand
you
Do you want to be named?
I'll help you with that.
Chi
What can my sister do?
N Life Deputy Editor
You know you're my friend, right?
that! One word, sister!
I'm there for you
I'll let you interview me
instead
When you broadcast
Let me appear as a sub
Well...
But what...
If my sister says to do it
Do you do it there?
I already told my friend everything
Well, as long as you like it
Are you going to push for it?
Don't if you don't like it
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
Ah, why are you so impatient?
Well...
It's not a medium I particularly like.
If only I could
Have you tried it?
Oh, really?
so?
What are the conditions?
First of all, to the vlog
Take pictures of your daily life and hand them over
While conducting the interview
I'm planning to take a pictorial as well.
If the picture comes out well
to the ground
I think it's possible
Okay!
Anyway, if you raise awareness of the show host,
Because sales also increase
Then
Yena, on the next broadcast
Is Najeong serving?
I think it's a bit fast, but
To raise people, you need to make bold investments.
I thought I might need it
Okay, good idea.
I put them together
Is there more synergy than expected?
Then
- Good job!
- Yes
What
Good job
So much for this shit
Don't be arrogant
Honestly, I also interviewed
in many places
I got a request
I was cutting it out because it was annoying?
Uh, uh, you see.
Well, anyway, I did my part.
Please don’t forget your promise.
Wow!
oh my god! oh my god! oh my god!
I'm doing it with Illy!
After...
My monthly life mask in Jeju Island is
Come to Sangmin
Could you please tell me to water the plants here?
But I like that opening
Isn't it a bit cliché...
- Here's your coffee!
- uh! Senior, senior!
Wow, why bother?
You don’t have to do this.
Ah, an intern should do this much.
- By the way
- Yes
How did you roast and boil Jena?
Did you win the sub position?
It just happened that way.
- Okay, everyone...
- Yes, yes
- Have a cup of coffee
- Thank you, I'll drink it well.
Here is Senior Jo Na-jeong
- Yes, caffeine transfusion.
- Wow!
You know the filming is today, right?
our company headquarters
To Studio A until 2pm
Mmmmm
I'll move on as soon as the meeting is over.
The vlog is
You're taking good pictures, right?
hello! yes
Today the entire staff gathered together
Set and Broadcast
discussing the whole thing
It's brainstorming day.
Say hello!
No, hey, I'm in a meeting.
What then?
Without notice
What are you doing now?
- Hey...
- What?
Everyone like this
Are you going to be uncooperative?
Are you saying this is good for me?
It's all for the company!
Now
Everyone be bright and excited, okay?
- I think they're doing it again.
- Yes
Hello!
yes hello
N Life subscribers!
Yes, it’s nice to meet you like this.
I'm so happy
Our Suite Home Shopping
Please love me a lot!
Please love me!
- and!
Sister!
It's been so long since we last
We go out together like this
Before, after work
You were busy running around having fun.
Uh, uh, right, right!
It was like that, it was like that!
Uh...it was really fun back then
Every day after the broadcast ends
Drinking alcohol, just...
I'm about to go on a trip
That's right
I learned a lot from you
Thanks to that, like this
I was able to grow
I really appreciate it.
Just in case, I told my sister
If there's something that made you sad
Please forgive me
As you know, I am a bit narrow-minded.
Oh, what!
Oh, that's right!
wait a minute!
I have something to give to my sister.
Wow...
Ah, this is me
I only wore it twice
For some reason, my sister
I think it would fit well
This thing is expensive!
As far as I can
I will be your mentor.
Lean on me now, okay?
Wow, thank you
Ouch!
I'm here!
Nothing bad happened, right?
Oh my
Um...
How are you feeling?
Are you feeling a bit frustrated because you don’t have a head?
Now it's time to come, but it's strange
As soon as I arrive
Beautiful beauty, you will get it back
uh
These days, they don’t say let’s do it.
I guess I've given up now, last time
He came in after finishing his drink.
I'm actually relieved.
Although I feel a little sorry
uh
I think so too
Jooyoung is such a model student.
About this perfect family
It seemed like he had his own standards.
Something like me when I was young
It looks like there is a wound
In a way
It's a bit disappointing
After listening to it
My father left home when I was a senior in high school.
-But still, my mother-in-law tells people...
-You crazy bastard...
Room...
Who was it just now?
Could it be you?
No way
Not you, right?
grow! You crazy guy!
No... honey, what are you doing here?
So what are you doing here?
me?
I...
Uh, I...
With my figures
Uh...
Oh, there's this.
Ah...
Oh, you must be very surprised, uh
So this is
It's long to explain.
Don't get me wrong, I mean...
Misunderstanding?
What misunderstanding?
you!
say it right
What on earth are these for?
Oh, what is it for?
These are my friends
There is no purpose
- Just with me since I was young...
- Then these are
Even before marriage
You mean it happened?
Well, his head
Why did you come by courier?
Don't you speak quickly?
That...
During the last flood, water filled the basement.
There was mold on Jessica's face.
What?
Jessica?
You perverted bastard!
Oh, what, what, what are you doing?
Let go! Don't you let go of this?
- I'm going to burn it all!
- Oh, no!
Let go, you pervert!
- It hurts, really!
- Let go!
omg!
Rebecca...
Rebecca!
No...
Rebecca...
I think you can do it like this
- Yes
- Next...
Is this okay?
- Can I even use this word?
- uh? Elijah!
uh? Are you here?
uh
This is Song Yena’s show host.
This is Deputy Editor Lee Il-ri.
Oh my! hello
We met before
Do you remember?
At the mall?
I told you at the time that you were a huge fan.
I told you
I heard a lot of words
inner intimacy
Yes?
uh!
Oh, where is the dressing room over there?
Please give me some guidance
yes, that way
I'll take you there
yes
Illy Lee
Kill your temper, okay?
What am I?
uh!
yes you are
thank you
Please change your clothes into this.
Oh my! So pretty
60's jackie style
Ouch! I like it
Thank you, Deputy Editor.
But, those aren't really empty words.
Sister, I'm a big fan.
I watched everything from the beginning
Really, really steamy fan
thank you
Especially that older/younger couple episode.
I really enjoyed listening to it
These days with my boyfriend
Are you bickering over contact?
We broke up a while ago
Oh my!
Sorry...
Ah, then
Shall I set you up on a blind date?
That's it
Oh, actually
As soon as I saw my father-in-law,
There's someone that comes to mind
He is the director of our partner company.
Of all the people I've ever met
The best in personality
Best manners
and
There's a lot of money too!
two buildings
Wait a minute
Now... age is
You're in your mid-40s now.
Ah, here it is
How do you feel?
why? Do you like it?
Ah, this
As a group, on Namhansanseong Mountain
I took this photo while I was eating boiled rice.
It did make me look a little old, though.
In real life, you look really handsome.
If it's that good
Yena said you would meet me.
There is a big age difference between me and you.
Your type is not my type
Uh...
Uh, you really don’t do that, Mr. Bu-pyeon?
As I heard
Very gaijinsang, very
How is it going?
Yes, it's going well.
Najeong is bigger than I thought.
Are you doing well?
I am quite satisfied as a mentee.
What else are you curious about?
Editors?
I'm curious about that
Why, in home shopping
They sell a lot of different products.
Well, the absurd customers
Actually, I think there are viewers.
Huh! There are a lot
This is not me
Our customer service people
You're having a hard time
For example, a product that has been used for about one or two months
There are many cases of returns.
For some ridiculous reason
There are a lot of cases where people ask for a return!
use it for a month or two
Are you returning it?
yes What, what
Shoes and clothes are basic.
In some cases, even the underwear you were wearing
Oh my god!
No, once
You were a customer who purchased sanitary pads.
As you know, it is sold on home shopping.
Sanitary pads are in huge quantity.
But suddenly you call me
Baby, you’re in menopause now.
There is no need for sanitary pads anymore!
This is ridiculous!
No, I'd rather
Buy pomegranate juice or something like this.
That's right! That's right!
uh! I
They also sold pomegranate juice.
Do you ever drink pomegranate juice?
Ah, these days
Well, menopause is happening faster, so even people in their 40s
At a management level
He ate a lot.
pomegranate juice
Really good for women
Highly recommended, highly recommended
But if you look at the show hosts,
You are very thin.
Always maintaining size 44 or 55
Stress is normal
I don't think so
What you usually do
Do you have any diet secrets?
I don't know
How did you get here?
I am so
Because I don’t have a fat body type.
Even if you eat whatever you want
Live broadcast for over an hour
When researching the market
Don't you have time to gain weight?
Rebecca!
crazy guy
Yes, representative.
You weren't there, where are you now?
I'm out after work.
What's going on?
Have you been drinking?
yes
Former team leader
Why is this happening all of a sudden these days?
Whatever happened in the past
The person who didn't make a hole
The report is late too
Leave your seat whenever you have time
Divorce anytime soon
I also heard rumors
Is that why you're so lost now?
Even if your personal life is complicated
It shouldn't interfere with work, right?
yes?
No, Mr. Representative.
What do you mean by that?
Anyway
This performance of ‘Kiss of the Spider Woman’
Because the foundation is also paying attention.
Come to your senses
Don't think about making excuses later!
Do you understand?
braided!
- Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work
But why do you speak so well?
- oh! Me?
- and!
Song Yena is completely improved.
I was so nervous today
- You did so well.
- So good, so good.
Actually, I am today
I was shaking and thought I was going to die
With Lee Il-ri, who is angry
Cheap Song Yena
I just put it on for no reason
I thought something was going on
Anyway
I'm so glad it ended safely.
Thanks, friend.
Not much to do
Why? What happened?
Sister! My husband!
Uh, uh
- You should have a drink with me too.
- Yes
- Now
- Ta-da!
Wow!
- Sister
- Yes
Thank you for holding such a great interview.
Thank you so much
I am also very grateful to my father-in-law.
Me, when I took a photo shoot today
I was really ecstatic
The clothes you wear every day
The makeup I wear every day
What were you so excited about?
No!
Usually it's not me
The product was the main character.
So
Even if I decorate the arm pretty?
I always serve
But
Today
I am the main character!
Ah, the main character
This is how it feels
- Oh!
- Uh, uh!
- Wow
- Oh my!
Sister, I'm sorry!
It's okay
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Wow, Mr.
But my father-in-law
The director earlier...
Is it really that bad?
yes
I don't have any plans to get married yet.
Wow! what?
Father, you are forty-one, right?
If you don't go now,
I guess I really can't go.
Why are you so unable to grasp reality?
and originally
The pain of this breakup
as someone else
It needs to be treated.
The harder it is
this person, that person
Do you need to meet me?
Ah, if you don't like it, you can't do it.
That's enough, that's enough
Let someone else do it, okay?
A little snow...
You seem to be very high-ranking, Mr.
Ah!
My husband, but
I have a favor to ask you.
I was talking about diet earlier.
Please edit that a little bit
Can I do it for you?
why?
That...
Ouch!
Oh, just edit it please.
When I looked at it, it didn't seem like a problem.
Don't worry, it doesn't matter
We'll cut it out ourselves.
Oh, what!
When celebrities ask for editing
You edit everything.
With a celebrity
Are you discriminating against the show host now?
Discrimination?
Is this discrimination or what?
Celebrities, huh?
Preview the edited version
Even receiving confirmation
I know everything too
No, to be honest, I was also upset.
I'm a public figure who makes a living.
Oh, don't do that, please edit it.
Song Yena!
Editing permission is
We have it, stop it!
Hey, Eli, talk to me.
What? What are you talking about?
Let's go out and do it, go out and do it
Uh, come on
Hey... Huh?
cadet!
What are you?
What do you think of people
Drag me out of my seat?
Then what becomes of me?
Hey, I'm asking you this
Just cut it off if you can.
It might be uncomfortable for him.
You told him today
Why are you being so servile?
Have you forgotten everything that happened to you?
Blinded by success
Things like pride
I guess they gave it to the dog?
I told that bitch
I told you not to bow down!
Stop it, Illy!
What should I do to stop?
Honestly, I didn't like him
Because it's your favor
I had no choice but to listen.
But
I can't thank you
How can this happen?
hey!
Yena!
Song Yena! let's talk with me
To that person
Did you gossip about me?
Ha...
Well then
I knew that
To fuck me from the beginning
Did you conspire with that woman?
What kind of nonsense is that?
What's wrong with that?
The broadcast was edited strangely.
You're doing it to bury me.
Something happened to me a long time ago
To get revenge!
Why are you writing a novel alone again?
yes
If you've been involved with your sister since long ago,
Nothing happened
The spotlight is always on
Keep it to yourself
Because he is a senior
Ignoring people and craving them
If I were your sister
Do you know how shaken I was?
What about you?
I'm neglecting work because of my child.
Talking about me behind people's backs
When asked to change teams
I'm really hurt!
What did I do for you?
At that time, my sister
It's true that it was a nuisance!
What kind of official position is a working mom?
yes
Working mom is not an official position.
But everyone lives
Sometimes things go well
There are times when I struggle
But you think this is an opportunity
Did you have to take me down so cruelly?
Same goes for you, now.
yes
I hated my sister, but still
For taking this opportunity
I was deeply grateful
So that's what it was like back then
I also felt a little sorry
But what is this?
Talking about people behind their backs?
You are no different from me.
- Elijah!
- senior!
Senior Illy, you went first.
Ah, Illya...
Illy Lee
Are you really not going to answer the phone?
Uh...
yesterday
Did you get in okay?
What happened?
Yenna serves herself
Yang Mi-sook as intern
I heard you asked me to change it?
what?
Uh, what does that mean?
Seonyoung says Yena
He said he couldn't broadcast with senior Cho.
Yang Mi-sook asked to borrow an intern.
Ah, until the preliminary meeting.
Leave a sub that everyone follows
Why would you do it with someone else?
Yena!
you
I cut it and Yang Mi-sook
Did you ask me to make you a sub?
yes
This is a different promise
If I give you an interview
They decided to make me a sub...
Call N Life Magazine
Interviewed
I told them not to let me out.
So
You don’t owe me anything anymore, right?
Right? This time too
The composition came out really well.
Right? So...
I once...
The general manager has arrived
yes
Do what you used to do
Everyone
You didn’t forget that we had a company dinner today, right?
- Yes
- Um
It’s been a while since interns came in.
I couldn’t even hold a welcome party.
Let’s eat something delicious later
Hmm...
Thank you for your hard work
Ah, but
What kind of general manager is that?
I'm the head of the broadcasting support division.
I'm the chairman's wife's niece.
Really?
Awesome
Everyone
In our sky class
I have a new friend
Now, Leah, to your friends.
Shall we say hello?
- Yes
- Yeah.
Hello?
My name is Juri-ae
Please take care of me
Then to your new friend
Please be nice.
Come on, Liae
Where is the locker...
here
The teacher will put your bag in your bag.
And, the seat is
here
My name is Minwoo Noh
I'm Juri-ae
Ooh!
Hey!
ruler!
Yang Mi-sook, who doesn't play while working
Yang Mi-sook, who never takes off her clothes when playing
- Thank you!
- Yes
Come on!
Each and every one of you
Don't forget that you are the face of the company.
life is sweet
Sales are also sweet
Sweet!
Home shopping!
Uh, I fed it.
And until it's too late
Don't let them play
Be sure to go to bed before nine o’clock
Okay
Ah! And Jun
I have to go to the bathroom before I go to bed
Otherwise, I will wrap you in a blanket.
Oh, I got it.
Yena, kid! really
The manager is drunk.
I'm not drunk, hey!
uh!
Grump!
- Najeong
- Oh, yes, yes.
Why are you here?
ah! Ah...
You are the general manager, uh...
Oh, Yena was there too?
Oh, I...
I was just making a phone call to my husband.
Ah...
Is Yena not feeling well?
My face color has been bad since a while ago.
My name is the head of the headquarters.
I have to take care of a friend like this
Yes, of course, of course.
- Come in, yeah.
- Yes, yes
What's going on?
Why is it useless?
It's meddling! In someone else's business
If you talk back and forth for no reason,
I really can't stand still
Ah!
If something is difficult
Come to my room anytime
thank you
Now
Our junior interns
Please lead me well
Now...
Okay, let's do it.
Uh, Wooram
My neck hurts so much
Are you at the hospital?
If you need confirmation
Leave a message
ok, good work
hello
Oh, I understand, Mom.
Okay, I won't run away.
I'll get a consultation first and then call you.
Why do you say you don’t like it?
Apply for consultation
Annoy people
Grade C?
With my looks, with this recognition
how do i get this job
Is it possible to get a C grade?
That's right
Your beauty and
When looking at awareness, etc.
You can never understand
But more than I thought
Fashion magazine reporter or YouTuber
in the marriage market
It's not my preferred occupation.
Lawyers, doctors, pharmacists, etc.
Lion turning is a grade A element.
Yes, yes, I know what you mean.
So
Is that the biggest problem?
Not
What, there's another problem?
Uh...
Crucially
A little older, that
It's difficult for you to have children.
I told you
I have no intention of having children.
Oh, yes, yes
We will do our best to meet your needs as best as possible.
A good man
I'll try searching.
Then, in matching
most importantly
What requirements do you think
Could you please tell me?
Uh...
Phil?
Oh, Phil?
Oh, I like Phil.
Yes, of course, it's important.
Yes, Phil
Phil!
Wow! What, really?
No, I drank yesterday
Is it really stretched out?
No, why do people
Make me wait two hours?
- Hey, Jjonnajeong.
- Yes
You, well, to Song Shoho.
Have you had any contact?
Yeah, there wasn't one?
you are your mentor
They say they can't contact me
Why are you so calm?
Anyway
Huh? Yes and now
Wanting only yourself to succeed
Just no change, no change
Wow, really
- Hello
- Huh? Senior! Are you here?
Oh, he really...
strange
Even though my personality is **
I'm a friend who never breaks a promise.
- Huh? Senior
- Yes
Have you not seen Song Ye-na?
Didn't you see it?
Oh, that's strange.
Why don't you keep answering the phone?
Uh, yeah, I didn't get it.
Maybe
Yes, if we meet
Mentee evaluation until today
Could you please tell me I have to submit it?
It can't be too late
Uh, okay
Ah, Taejeong!
Well then, I'm not answering the phone.
Should I go to Jena’s house?
Let’s talk about the mentee evaluation.
Yes, you do.
I guess that would be nice
Yeah
Save me...
Oh!
hello! Yena!
So...
It hurts...
What's going on? Yena!
Yena!
I'm in front of your house right now!
Could you please open the door?
Yena!
What's wrong with you?
Our Yena
Boat whales are big, right?
Should I try some fries?
I want to eat black bean noodles
I want to eat sweet and sour pork
Wow!
Ha...
Huh?
Yena, are you awake?
why are you like this
Do you often surprise people?
You almost died, you!
What happened?
I have intestinal obstruction
I had emergency surgery.
How long so far
I wish I hadn't eaten that much
They asked me if we were friendly with each other.
Somehow
I don't eat even a single grain of rice
He only drinks Americano a lot.
But
What about you?
Misook and Taejeong
I can't contact you
So it was a little strange
You’re the type of person who doesn’t usually break promises.
It's been a few days already
My complexion is also a bit bad.
So it bothered me a bit.
So
Did you come to my house?
He is my mentor by name and name.
What if something happens?
So
I got scared
You came running like crazy, right?
now
It's a bit hard to say this, but
I'm sorry about what happened last time
But I too from the beginning
I didn't mean to swear at you
When you said you didn't want to work with me
Where can I complain?
But to the people at the company
I can't say it
To my closest friends
I just said I was complaining.
Well, anyway...
If I hurt your feelings, I apologize.
I'm sorry
lighten up my mood
Huh?
You...
Are you crying?
I don't know
My sister doesn't know
how hard it was for me
I almost died from exhaustion too.
My sister is married and has a child.
I also have a husband
I have no husband and no children.
Now all that's left is real work
Like a greedy person again
They come to take my place
I said I hated my sister.
I hated it so much
It's absurd, it's absurd
One crazy kid
I was hired by the wrong company
What kind of disgrace is this?
That's right
Why do you say such absurd things?
Did you get hatched?
The work has become so unnecessary!
If this goes on, there will be a court battle
It's obvious that he's going to end up in a mess.
What is it?
how
Because you keep seeing Seonmin.
Would you like to talk directly?
yes?
why?
Did you think I didn't know?
You, him...
He also introduces me to jobs here and there.
He said he was comforting me and doing that.
So people
Aren’t you whispering and being rude?
I told him to leave, but he didn’t listen until the end!
you! If it continues like this
me too
I can't wait any longer
An employee who tries to stab a knife in the company, etc.
Which company would just leave it alone!
Not only that?
If this happens because of you
I'm doing well at the company
Even Na-jeong is being harmed.
Become the head of the household
Even my innocent wife
Do you want to get cut? you?
PD
I...
I'm waiting at the cafe in front of you
Wait a minute
See you
Me again?
- why?
- We discussed it.
Seonyoung instead of Yena
While pinch hitting
No experience in serving
What Misook does
It's too dangerous
From a partner company
I won't stay still
The pre-meeting was also conducted by a senior.
Because I've done it all
Just a senior again
I think it would be better if you sub
Why, why?
Do you hate it?
Uh, no
Of course not
Uh, uh
- Uh
- Hey, you
Come out to the cafe in front of the office for a moment
Because I have something to say
You can talk about it at work
Why do you want people to come out?
You are among the interns at the company.
Growling...
Do you want to show me? Ah!
This...
Baby?
Uh...
Hey, what are you doing here?
Then you
What are you doing here?
The show host from earlier during the day
Tears and snot in front of me
It was all crazy?
You already
It was broadcast once!
You, to me
Say you'll give in
Mom! she's my girlfriend
Mom, this is my boyfriend.
Wow!
No, what happened?
grown baby
That, on the street
So, are you crying sadly?
Hey! do you like me
- Why is this happening, really?
- I live with myself.
It was so suffocating
So now I
With my husband back
I received preferential treatment
- Are you thinking?
- back to work
Even if you want to start, there is no opportunity...
Interview and that's it now
What does it matter?
You are me
You said that when we first met
Already in the suite
I'm supposed to work!
What?